'2026'
'2026
Election day'
'At a time when elections are
in full swing across Tamil Nadu'
'Due to caste issues
residents of Pappampatti village'
'Boycotted the election for the 3rd time'
[siren wailing]
Get ready, all of you
Come and vote
The right to vote is the civic duty
of every Indian citizen to uphold
Sir, we are ready to vote
But knowing none of us
will vote for their Party
They have denied us
the right to vote freely, sir
See the fate of those
who defied them and voted
[dramatic music]
We can't vote one day and then
live in fear the whole year through, sir
They will hit us
even if we go to school, sir
We will be so terrified
My dear child, whenever I feel scared
I will think of one man's story
Immediately my fear will vanish
and my heart will brim with courage
Shall I narrate that story of courage?
That Mr Courage is
'Thalapathy'
'VI'
[upbeat music]
'J'
'AY'
Honorable
Tamil Nadu
Chief Minister
Honorable Chief Minister of Tamil Nadu
C Joseph Vijay
Thalapathy C Joseph Vijay
'Madurai
2013'
[gate opens]
[suspenseful music]
[mobile ringing]
Tell me, Narayanan
Sir, 20 rowdies have surrendered here
Shall I proceed with the admission
or wait until you get here?
I am shifting my quarters
I won't be coming right now
Complete the formalities
- 'Take them to Admission Block'
- Okay, sir
[suspenseful music intensifies]
[phone ringing]
Is there any important prisoner
in Admission Block?
Yes, sir
'Loganathan
Business man'
'Opposition's key funder'
'He has been locked up
under a put-up case'
STOP THEM!
[alarm blaring]
[thrilling music]
[gates closing]
I am on the way
What's the situation?
Sir
Take your time
They have gone into C Block
So...?
Thalapathy is there, sir
[continuous commotion]
'Indian Democracy'
[thuds]
[grandiose music]
[grandiose music continues]
[man screaming]
[short whistle]
Hey! Kill him
[snaps finger]
'Bro, 1 minute'
'When you were
playing hide & seek'
'You knocked down this grandpa
and disturbed his sleep'
'Make sure our grandpa gets his due rest'
'Then continue your game'
Game, huh?
Hey! We plan to kill now
Turn back and go
This seems to be a new struggle
First, make him rest in peace, da
[suspenseful music]
[sharp thuds]
[thuds and thwacks]
[enthralling music]
[fire sparkling]
[theme song plays]
'JANA NAYAGAN'
'PEOPLE'S LEADER'
[sharp music]
[sharp music continues]
If you didn't hear me clearly
I'll repeat it for your ears
Grandpa has to sleep
Lord and master!
I am your slave
First, grandpa has to rest in ease
Only then, Logan Baba will rest in peace!
Okay?
Go back, da
Grandpa, lie on a human water bed
How does it feel?
Cool and comfy, uh?
Sleep, my child
If you sing me a lullaby
I'll happily slip into dream world
What, thatha?
- You seem to be in a jolly mood!
- [chuckles]
What are you gaping at me for?
Sing, I say
"Grandpa, just a pinch I need
Give me your snuff powder, I plead"
"Grandson, pass my stick,
I'll whack you double quick"
"Grandpa, just a pinch I need
Give me your snuff powder, I plead"
"Grandson, pass my stick,
I'll whack you double quick"
"When grandpa grabbed his stick to hit
the snuff powder flew into thin air, swift"
"Grampsssss"
Hey!
I asked you to sing for thatha to sleep
you're making him dance and leap!
HEY!
- Hey... hey!
- Shhhhh!
What? Going overboard?
My bro came here on a killing mission
You want him to preach now!
[mocks]
[smacks]
- [sharp kicks]
- 'Aiyaiyo!'
[song from 'Kadhalukku Mariyadhai' plays]
Bingo! He'll sleep like a baby now
"Will she sing me a lullaby?"
"Rest my head in her bosom like a baby?"
"Will she move with flowing grace
as a golden chariot to this place?"
"Or disappoint my heart
by drifting apart?"
Hey wait... wait
"Be patient, sing no more
I can hear him snore"
'He is fast asleep'
[loud snore]
- [thwacks]
- [man screams softly]
[blows out]
"The entire town is in slumber deep"
"Even the cool breeze has started to sweep'
"But sleep eludes this blessed grandfather"
"Wonder why, I'm clueless, brother"
Bro! I told you to close his chapter
You are partying, singing together?
- Sssshhh!
- HUH?
Hey!
[quiet whisper]
Grandpa is sleeping
Keep quiet
What is this, bro?
You keep saying 'grandpa... sleep'?
- Move aside, bro
- [sharp kicks]
"Death's quiet whisper
drifted into my ear"
"It appeared here as an image
of a king with confidence and courage"
[winces]
[gripping energetic music]
[sharp thwack]
[loud thud]
Listen to the advice of youngsters, da
[gripping energetic music continues]
Hai!
[action ensues]
[gripping energetic music continues]
Telling us to make him sleep
You'll end up making us rest in peace!?
'Please open the door'
He is very dangerous
Arrest them
This is the best time to act
With issues overlapping
we can finish him off
- [crowd cheering]
- [ominous music]
Problem is spiraling
Open the gate
Sir
Till now
They have tried to kill him 20 times
But even to edge close to him
They have to go past
Vanamaran and Nelamaran
Escape from the threatening gaze
of Kadamban and Kangeyam
Retaliate to the power
of Murugan and Velan
'I got a gang'
'We run the space
Bang bang'
'Say, what?'
'I got a gang'
'We run the space
Bang bang'
[upbeat music]
The day he was arrested
and brought here
Not only inside the jail, sir
Even outside, they settled
as an army to protect him
Thalapathy is not
under our protection, sir
Just the opposite, we are
under Thalapathy's protection
'I got a gang'
'We run the space
Bang bang'
Sir... sir
You staked your life to save mine
Thank you, sir
I won't sit quiet watching
any crime happening around me
I will show up
Sir... er, may I know your name?
[heroic music]
- Narayanan
- 'Sir?'
I want to see his files
[pulsating music]
[dusting off]
You hit a battalion of prisoners
Are you Superman?
[pulsating music continues]
[upbeat music]
I am an ordinary man, baby
But I have heard people say
whatever I do is sooper!
Then you are proper 'Superman' in my eyes
Dishum!
[playful giggle]
Dishum-dishum
Is his mother the reason
for him being here in jail?
'Yes, sir'
'Not enough if you keep lamenting
you want to see your son'
Take your tablets regularly
if you want to see your son
Atleast till your son comes
You would've asked for bail
at least 50 times or so?
Did they release him?
She won't last long
Doubtful if she will see her son
No medicine is holding
my breath, doctor
Love
One last wish to see my son
I will die only after I see him
Sir, I'm begging you
I'll fall at your feet
If you send our brother home
Happily his mother will breathe her last
knowing she could see her son, sir
Sir, they will wait with folded hands daily
when the previous jailer comes and leaves
They didn't disperse
even when they were hit
Direct orders from higher-ups
What can we do, sir?
If I want to see my amma
you'll say she isn't here
Superman's mother is alive
Let's take him
to see his mother, pa
[emotional music]
Narayanan
We are going to the forest
with Vetri tomorrow
Okay?
Son hearing his mother's cries of pain
Crosses all barriers to see her again
As the scars healed today
Wind too parted the way
He is returning to bloom
in his mother's womb
Back to the magic of my motherly lap
Those childhood memories wrap
to replay in my mind's map
A sky that vanished into the horizon
Now returns as life's very reason
My world spins again in a magical way
Because you are my heart's mainstay
My heart anew
brims with love so true
Even if I die, I will live with you
[sniffles]
[emotional music continues]
My poignant poetry
My tears of misery
All reflect you in my story
In my next birth, when I am a mother
Even then you will be my child, no other
My amma passed away
after seeing my face, sir
You fulfilled my mother's last wish
How will I thank-
Thank you, sir
Superman, don't feel bad
you lost your amma
I'll be your amma hereafter
[emotional music intensifies]
Aah, open your mouth
Your daughter looks smart
in army uniform, sir
Yeah
Actually my wife wanted
to join the military very badly
Her parents didn't accept our love and
tried to get her married to someone else
She cast her dream aside
and married me
And
She passed away
in last year's riot
Every time she wore that uniform
and saw her reflection in the mirror
I used to feel guilty
maybe I ruined her dreams
After she was born
She used to keep saying, 'I will
make your dream come true, ma'
At least if she joins the military
I thought my feeling of guilt
will slowly disappear, but
Why, sir?
What happened?
[loud thud]
[panic attack]
[heavy exhaling]
It's okay
It's okay, dear
[heavy exhaling continues]
Seeing her mother die in flames in the riot
if she hears any unexpected loud sound
Fear phobia gets triggered like this
How can she join the army?
Girls should never be scared, sir
Viji should be raised like a tigress
- [chiseling]
- [saddening music]
Wow!
Viji dear
Fear should never
dictate the way we live
Make fear and
The peddlers of fear
Flee in panic
You should stand fearlessly like this
Only then this world will listen to you
- Huhm?
- Hmmhmmm!
- Stand fearless?
- Oho!
'Swasnia
Africa'
[continuous digging]
[villainous music]
'Himmler is en route'
'Get the gallows ready'
'Come soon, the whole jail
is waiting to kill him'
[villainous music continues]
'He destroyed our country, kill him'
[crowd clamor]
[villainous music continues]
'Tomorrow you will hang
in front of our President'
'Any last wish?'
'Go and ask your President
He'll be the one hanged to death'
[continuous gunfire]
'Civil war erupted'
'President was arrested
by the revolutionaries'
'Govt of Swasnia has
collapsed once again'
'A wave of panic has
swept across Swasnia'
- Shoot him immediately
- Yes, sir
[upbeat villainous music]
[cars speeding through]
[helicopter engine]
'HIMMLER'S MERCENARIES ARE COMING'
GET AWAY!
THEY WILL KILL ALL OF US!
[upbeat villainous music continues]
'All prisoners'
WHOEVER KILLS HIM
EARNS THEIR FREEDOM
RIGHT NOW
[alarm blaring]
[crowd screaming]
Hey! Like how you killed my people
I WILL KILL YOU THE SAME WAY
COME OUT
COME OUT, DA
[bam]
[upbeat villainous music]
[cracks neck]
[bones crack]
[chorus of angry voices]
- [bashing noises]
- [men groaning in pain]
[upbeat villainous music continues]
[continuous stabbing]
HEY! MOVE
I WILL BEAT HIM TO A PULP
[agitated crowd noise]
- MOOOVE!
- [vehicle engine starts]
MOOOOVE!
- [missile firing]
- [loud explosion]
- [crashes]
[upbeat villainous music continues]
[vans swirling in]
[crashes]
[agitated crowd noise]
[continuous gunfire]
Sorry for the delay, my friend
It will be done in 5 minutes
[continuous gunfire]
- [sinister music]
- [continuous gunfire]
Shoot him
[exploding]
[continuous gunfire]
[tanks firing]
[sinister music]
[gunfire]
Move
'Leak the video to the media
of this President being hanged to death'
'Is all this unwanted emotions,
attention needed at this point?'
Saddam Hussein being hanged
by the Americans is not a big deal at all
'Saddam Hussein'
'If you try to oppose me'
'This will be your fate' USA said
That is the point to note
Fear must be instilled into Governments
It's a statement
[snaps fingers]
- [man groaning]
- [upbeat villainous music]
Mr President
Whoever comes to kill me
Even if he summons
the entire world to do so
Every single one of them
I will kill everyone
and destroy everything
Only then I will die
[continuous gunfire]
[upbeat villainous music continues]
'Himmler, we have ensured
your photo is nowhere online'
'We were maintaining
it as a close secret'
'How did the President
get to know everything?'
Ubuntu
She has collected all the evidence about
our network and given it to the President
'If Himmler's arrest gets leaked
all of us will be caught in toto'
'What do you intend doing, Victor?'
No need to worry
Everything is under our control in Swasnia
'Himmler, whatever you asked is ready here'
'What is your plan?'
M-M!
'Breaking News! Swasnia has fallen
after an anonymous group-'
Sir has been missing for a week
Where is he, sir?
I told you already
Er... he has gone out of town
A policeman hiding the truth is wrong, sir
'For flouting the rules and
taking you to see your mother'
'Sir has been suspended and
ordered to vacate his quarters'
'You will feel terrible if you find out
So he asked me not to tell you'
'Before he left'
'In the list of prisoners
being freed on August 15th'
'He added your name too'
[emotional music]
[emotional music continues]
Sorry, sir, I'll send
my daughter to Day Care
And somehow
join duty today, sir
Yes, sir
[emotional music continues]
'Surprise!'
Hai! Superman
Viji sweetypie?
Fever?
Hmmmm
Aiyiayo!
Viji... aa
What's up, Vetri?
Sir, if you had told me
your job will be at stake
I would have never gone
to see my mother, sir
Even I know the pain of a mother
who is separated from her son, Vetri
Dishum-dishum
- Dishum
- Awwww!
Not leaving, Vetri?
I should, sir
I have a very important task to finish
I wanted to see you before that
Viji, get ready
I'll drop her in Day Care
I have to go up to Head Quarters
No way! I want to
be here with Superman
Superman, till my appa returns
won't you be here with me?
You go, sir
I'll take care of her
I can assure you Viji sweety won't
shed a single drop of tear
I'll take good care of her
till you get back home
Vetri, don't open this door
I have stored Viji's mother's stuff here
If she sees all that, reminded of
her amma, she'll get scared, okay
[melodious music]
Bye
Sir?
Sir, I'm on my way
I'll be there in 10 minutes
- [loud crash]
- [glass shatters]
[gut wrenching music]
[sobbing inconsolably]
I'll eat only when appa comes back
I don't want to eat
I'll go to school
only when I see my appa
[gut wrenching music continues]
[panic attack]
- [heavy breathing]
- Viji... Viji?
Look over there
[continuous heavy breathing]
'Todaiiiin!
Don't get scared'
'Here I am, your forever friend'
'Smile!'
'He hee he hee he!'
I am her forever friend
She will listen only to me
'I will strangle your Adam's apple'
'Come into the kitchen
I'll make mincemeat out of you'
'Aiyaiyo!'
'He is biting me
SOS! Save me'
[confused music]
Hai
'Ouch!'
'What a strong blow!'
'Bowled over!'
[snickering]
'Oof! Don't puff into my face!'
[tinkling laughter]
[melodious music]
Beauty blessed from above
with million moons in tow
If a million poems were compiled
their meaning is you, my child
A million boons combined
To be a godsend; precious find
Your tiny giggles infectious
Nudges me to enjoy life vivacious
Pupil of my eye, my princess
Eyelid to my eye, so precious
You bloomed in my palm gracious
You reside in my heart and shine
Not by birth, but Destiny's child of mine
You are my world; my everything
My pet child, my darling
She's physically alright
But you must give 100% courage
to your child and bring her up real brave
Only then she will be
cured of her fear phobia
'Otherwise it can turn out to be fatal'
Superman?
How do I call you?
Whatever name you like
You can call me 'uncle'
Or 'chithappa' in Tamil
Or 'chitha' as short name
Chitha?
I like that
Then call me 'chitha'
But whenever you are
in trouble of any kind
Think of 'appa'
in your tiny heart
[whooshes]
Wherever I am, I will
come rushing in front of you
Pupil of my eye, my princess
Eyelid to my eye, wondrous
You bloomed in my palm precious
I can't
Ta-dain!
Come
Okay?
Uncs, no... no
My steps follow you all the way; wherever
My shoulders were made to lift you higher
Non-stop stories, you should tell me
with your youthful eyes expressively
We shall close the door on world's face
Just you and me as family always
Even without you asking me to
I am ready to give my life for you
Pupil of my eye, my princess
Eyelid to my eye, so precious
You bloomed in my palm gracious
You reside in my heart and shine
Not by birth, but Destiny's child of mine
You are my world; my everything
My pet child, my darling
Chitha
Pupil of my eye, my princess
Eyelid to my eye, wondrous
You bloomed in my palm, precious
Speed up to find Karthik
before he enters his class
[hissing sound]
Suresh, call Karthik
Hey dude
[smooches]
New movie
Coming?
Ex-am!
You go
PAH!
Sir, Assistant Commissioner
will be coming now
So what? Will he
rap me on my knuckles?
Get lost!
Speed up, only 10 minutes
for the film to begin
[sinister music]
[collision]
Won't you drive carefully?
[sinister music continues]
Get up, pay for over speeding
- And go
- Hey... hey!
Buy a bottle of water, go
Poor thing, sir
Go, man
Your parents?
They work in a private company, sir
My parents aren't alive
My dad's younger brother
Give me your phone
Shall I call your uncle and tell him
you're happily cutting class and roaming?
Aiyo! No need, sir, please
I'll pay the fine
for over speeding, sir
Over speed, huh?
You crashed into my car
and tried to kill me
Attempt to murder
Section # 307
Get into my car
Why, sir?
HEY! GET IN, DI
[heavily breathing]
Baby
Why are you panicking?
Nice and easy
I have to interrogate you
You go, I'll make my 'inquiry'
and send her back
[gripping music]
[mobile ringing]
I am at work
Anything important, dear?
'Aunt, serious problem'
- Hello, Pallavaram police station
- Will you arrest for over speeding?
Shall I call your boss?
Who is that Inspector?
Get him on the line
Inspector is yet to come, ma'am
'Asst Commissioner speaking'
I haven't arrested
anyone like that, sir
He's a sick guy
He has already been
suspended 4 times
Please do something
[gripping music continues]
Maara...?
Don't be scared
Be with me in the guest house
for a while and then I'll send you home
Okay?
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Whatever you intend doing with Viji
Find out my name
'Check with your department
and then make your move'
[confusing music]
[mobile ringing]
'Arms Depot
Tamil Nadu Police'
'My dear old man'
'I sent you a name on your phone
Tell me his horoscope'
[mass music]
- Hope you didn't try your tricks?
- 'Why?'
Is he such a top cat?
You would have heard of a killer
with many notches of murder
Have you heard of a top notch pro
who beats his own record?
[mass music intensifies]
[explosion]
That is 'Thalapathy' for you!
[mass music continues]
[mobile ringing]
Sir... sir
You will have 2 shadows
following you from tomorrow
One is your own
The other is mine
Hereafter you will live with fear
clinging to you as your second skin
You will die a slow death
fervently wishing you would rather die
'Your painful death will then be'
A lesson well learnt for any scum wanting
to abuse a girl physically in this world
Sir?
'Sister' will be at your doorstep
in a short while, sir
I will drop her myself, sir
No need
My daughter wanted to watch a movie
Take her to the theater
and bring her back safe
[mass music continues]
Jai Balayya!
[watching 'Daaku Maharaaj']
[mass music continues]
Sir... sir, forgive me, sir
Never again will I look
at any girl in a lustful way, sir
I have a soft corner
for the police department
[thrilling music]
Go
Isn't it wrong to cut class
to go and watch a movie?
[playful music]
Fine, forget it
This is the age to enjoy
When else will you bunk?
[playful music continues]
You missed a good movie
Real mass, too good
We watched in real life
with even more mass appeal, di
Viji?
Is your 'chitha' married?
No... why?
Simply... just for GK!
[gunshot firing]
Yov! Mai Pa
Saw this?
100 volunteers stand guard
protecting me even when I pee!
They ridicule you saying, 'can't find
your Party even with the help of a torch'
Blow your trumpet for all this
But having come from down south
you are stirring up Tamil Nadu
It's not an easy job, you know
Pluck out a few peanut roots
We can snack on the nuts
Yov... hey!
- Why did you throw it away?
- You want to eat the leaves too?
Pick it up
Re-plant it
Understood?
Peanuts stolen from there
Hid it from the gardener
and replanted here
Come
When you are so good
at such scientific conspiracies
You should have ruled Tamil Nadu
at least for 10 years
Time is not yet ripe!
2 parties are taking turns
looting the treasury
People are not thinking radically
to allow the 3rd party also to loot
50 pairs of hands raid
the wine shop in one go
Where will you see
a radical change?
Life is a pre-recorded cassette
Who can change that?
Forget it
On the way, shall we
cool down with a beer?
No need, man
I have a cold
Let's have a hot drink
'PAKISTAN'
'Children and elders'
All Indians are our enemies
'Kill them without an iota of mercy'
Move... faster, faster
MOVE
[continuous gunfire]
If everything goes smooth
according to our plan
Indian History will remember us always
with fear written on their pages
[continuous gunfire]
[screeching halt]
Get in the boat
Come on, get in the boat
'Fast... fast'
[gripping music]
'We have reached the ship'
Stop
[gripping music continues]
'A ship heading toward Tamil Nadu
has been hijacked'
'No clue what their plan is'
'Stop that ship and
seize it immediately'
Copy
[gripping music continues]
'Coastal area, India'
'Stop the ship'
'We have to inspect'
Last warning
'All of you, surrender immediately'
'We have to board your ship'
'Stop the ship'
They have surrounded the ship, bhai
'What to do now?'
- [groovy villainous music]
- 'Relaaax'
'Let's play a game'
Be serious, bhai
If the ship is caught
our entire plan goes phut!
I said, 'relax'
Forget the ship
Come
Let's play a game
[muffled gunfire]
[thrilling music]
Riaz
Where is the main guy?
[Hindi] I'll show you
Move... move
'What are these boxes?
Open them'
[thrilling music continues]
Where is all this going?
Going to make Pakistan out of India!
Everyone listens only to his command
[bashing]
[ominous music]
[chest opens]
What is M-M?
'Tell me what is M-M'
Shall I show you a trailer?
[hits]
[continuous gunfire]
[glass shatters]
[stabs]
Betrayal breaks your heart
[continuous stabbing]
[villainous music]
Salman
At least now
let's start the game
[presses button]
[firing sounds]
Sir, don't know where
the bullets are being fired from
[man groans]
[machine creaking]
[continuous gunfire]
[loud explosions]
[pulsating music]
[multiple explosions]
[continuous gunfire]
[pulsating music continues]
- [continuous gunfire]
- [multiple explosions]
[pulsating music continues]
[gun firing]
[gun fires]
[thrilling music]
Captain
Do you like the trailer?
'Let go of me'
'Let me go!'
You touched my dress
Your corpse will be hoisted like a flag
making a statement worldwide
- [loud explosion]
- Ready, Captain?
- [thrilling music continues]
[multiple explosions]
'Chief Secretary
Tamil Nadu'
Election is fast approaching
Let us not refer to Pakistan
as 'Muslim terrorists'
'We won't get votes'
We strongly condemn this attack
We extend our full support
to the Union Govt on this matter
My heartfelt condolences to the families
of the heroes who lost their lives
This attack proves the collapse
of Central and State governance
'Pudhiya Desam Party Office'
'Escalation of Islamic terrorism in India'
'Roja Rangaswamy's vehement accusation'
'Prime Minister directs deployment
of forces along the Pakistan border'
'Borderline war tension flares'
'So far, 100 bodies have been recovered'
'The Navy has raised concern
over its struggle to recover 60 bodies'
[gripping music]
'Global nations condemn
the terrorist attack strongly'
'The US President calls
for measures to prevent war'
Welcome, future CM
'Pakistan strongly condemns India
for making baseless accusations'
[sharp music]
My dear man
Imagine if the trailer
is trending worldwide
Main picture?
It will be a BLAST!
30th day from today
Final strike of M-M will begin
[sharp music continues]
To prevent that
Impossible for anyone
in this world to do so
[mass music]
[heavily panting]
Hi, chitha
Thank God!
Let me ride pillion
[screeching halt]
Viji, only 1 km more
Come on, run
Chitha
I can't do this, uncs
[playful music]
I am not set for all this, please
Run... run
Come on, come on
Raise your leg
Punch, punch
Force not enough, harder
- Abbaaa!
- Viji
100 push-ups
3 rounds, total 300
You should be drenched
with sweat by now
I'll go get milk
Hey Karuppu
- I'll take care
- Okay, anna
Why stop with 100?
I'll do 200 push-ups, chitha
You want to see sweat as proof?
Watch how I bring it on
[heavily panting]
One
Finished so soon?
I did, uncs
Look how I'm sweating
She's lying
[playful music]
Collaboration, huh?
Asked simply
If that isn't sweat
As if water from that bucket?!
[playful music continues]
At least this year sign properly
in the army application form
Hey! Sweetie pie
Viji sweety
Haven't I been signing
for 3 years, uncs?
This time too
I will sign for sure
[playful music continues]
'Anna'
What did she write this time, anna?
What was it last time, da?
'Car means fast
If Thalapathy hits, blast'
'If others speak, speech'
'If Thalapathy talks, reach'
Were you the brainbox behind this?
[suspenseful music]
Divya, we have run
out of batter in the fridge
- Refill some more
- 'Okay, anna'
[lively music]
HI!
Hi
Er-
Kayal
Journalist?
Ah... yes
How are you, aunty?
'Aunty', huh?
You look 40 plus
What are you then?
Ilaya Thalapathy?
- Call me 'Kayal'
- Okay, aunty
Why did you push him, da?
Apologize to him, let go
[whistling in style]
Everyone is watching
Give it to me
[lively music continues]
Sorry
Being a journalist
How do you do all this?
I've done M Phil
in Criminal Psychology
Having dealt with
so many criminals
This is
A piece of cake
I don't know
At this age
I don't know how to ask you
Age is just a number?!
Speak your heart and mind out
Viji is refusing to sign
the army application form
Try some magic trick like this
and make her sign, please
Sign?
[frolicky music]
I swear I won't sign
That's for sure, Kayal
But I will lend you my full support
[frolicky music continues]
- [waves crashing]
- [heavily panting]
Enough, chitha
DO IT!
[somber music]
Do it
Army is not meant for me
Listen to me
Try to understand
You keep giving me
excuses all the time
My training won't work for you
As soon as you finish your exams
you will join the Academy, confirmed
[somber music continues]
Why did you come here, Kayal?
To help uncs get his way?
No
I came to help you
You sign
Then fail in the physical test
After that what can he do?
[somber music continues]
- YES!
- But
She can't ace this
as long as she has fear phobia
If she tries, everything is possible
- No-
- Shhhhhhhh!
This is a time to celebrate
Come, let us start our concert!
[peppy music]
V for Victory, stage is set
Thalapathy event
you'll never forget
V for Victory, stage is set
Thalapathy's show you'll never forget
Hey you, look over there
Our anna's name with fan fare
Shining bold and bright
Slo Mo blazing great guns in sight
Nanba, nanbi, kiddies, listen to me
Join hands with trust; in unity
Time is right for us to move
A new dawn of hope in view
Don't live for yourself, with blinkers on
Don't let your worth be dimmed by anyone
Here comes our hero strong
To set right the wrong
Move…move aside
Thalapathy worldwide
Blast!
Blast!!
V for Victory, stage is set
Thalapathy event you'll never forget
Come one and all, welcome, world
Shall we vibe with magic unfurled?
Our commander's real presence
A cherished concert in every sense
Let our flag soar up in the sky
Host a feast, celebrate in style, high 5
Hey buddy
Are you ready?
Let crackers blast, full on fire
Let our flag rise even higher
The moment you enter
hurdles in fear shudder
Steady
Smile, buddy
Eyes spark fire with intensity
Pave a new path for posterity
In the Hall of Fame
to sing Thalapathy's name
This song is our tribute to Thalapathy
Anyone as awesome as anna; show me
This song is for our defender
Anyone like my brother
Point your finger!
Hey! A mighty land free
stands like a solid tree
See our sweat watering its root sturdy
Atop the tree lies a nest
Mother Nature's creation is this forest
Unite together
every brother and sister
No caste-bias whatsoever
Across our motherland
like your friendship grand
I have never seen such a bond
so endearing and beyond
Here comes our leader
To set right the wrong; not philander
My gem of a Thalapathy
Blast!
Blast!!
V for Victory, stage is set
Thalapathy event you'll never forget
Come one and all, welcome, world
Shall we vibe with magic unfurled?
Our leader's real presence
A cherished concert in every sense
Let our flag soar up in the sky
Host a feast, celebrate in style, high 5
This song is for our favorite leader
Anyone like anna; point your finger
This song is for our beloved leader
Anyone like our brother
Show me anyone
Point your finger!
My brother...!
This song is our tribute to Thalapathy
Anyone as awesome as anna; show me
This song is for our treasured leader
Anyone as able as our brother
point your finger
- Anna?
- What, da?
One laaast dance?
[indulgent laughter]
Okkaaay, da
Beat it
Speed it up, bro
Master coming!
Move aside
Enjoy the ride
Ace it!
Blast!
Blast!!
Where are they?
Both are missing
[chuckling]
They seemed to have 'clicked'
[ominous music]
[petrified screams]
'Viji'
'Viji, what are you doing?'
Listen to me
Viji, why are you so furious
looking at that toy?
I've never seen you in a rage like this
Let go of that toy
Viji, listen to me
'Viji'
[shrieks of fury]
[ominous music continues]
'Over 150 Navy officers
were killed by Pakistan terrorists'
'Unrecovered bodies have
washed ashore on the beach, Manali'
'NIA special team officer Mr Sangaram
has arrived at the spot to investigate'
'Secure the crime scene, boys, immediately'
[suspenseful music]
Boys
This is a part of a modern weapon
This was not an ordinary attack
It's
RC War
My God!
'Remote Control war?'
- Yes
- 'Can you confirm this?'
Ved
- Check the manufacturers
- Yes, sir
Sir, it's a Chinese company
Gingee Electronics
Get the details
[suspenseful music continues]
Sir
Bout Enterprises
They have supplied
to this African company
There isn't a single detail
about this company online, sir
'Check in Dark Web'
'Sir, not even in Dark Web, sir'
Wait... wait... wait
'That video, down'
'Open it'
'Find that ID
and send a DM'
'Refugee Camp
Swasnia'
[gripping music]
'Who are you?'
'Why are you asking about
Bout Enterprises?'
'In the Navy attack in our country'
[gripping music] continues
Who owns Bout Enterprises?
'The man who turned
our country to a graveyard'
'John Himmler'
'The Man of Death'
Can you tell us details about him?
'I have all the evidence against him'
'Sending right now'
- [explosion]
- [continuous gunfire]
[crowd wailing]
[heart wrenching music]
Annihilation!
Hey Allah!
'Before he turns India into Africa'
'Stop him immediately'
Excuse me
From this moment
I'll handle this case
[gun fires]
SIRRR!
[continuous gunfire]
[mechanized robot firing]
Move... move
Team, escape
Protect the evidence and weapons
Go, don't come out
till you hear my order
[smoke hissing]
[gun firing]
[thrilling music]
Cha!
Scientist Khaleel and team shot
the officer who came to interrogate
And escaped taking with them
the weapons belonging to the Military
'Scientist Khaleel who played a key role
as brain behind the naval strike'
'Evidence has been seized
about his training in Pakistan'
'Govt has announced a sum of Rs 10 million
as prize for clues about terrorist Khaleel'
[continuous gunfire]
No, no... don't!
'You will slip into
hypnotherapy now'
'No one is forcing you'
[emotional music]
'You can come out of this
at any point of time you want'
[emotional music continues]
Close your eyes
'You are in safe hands'
[whispering tone]
'As you relax'
'You are feeling more
and more comfortable'
Now, open your eyes
And slowly look at the monitor
[emotional music continues]
'Where is the toy
you bought from our shop?'
I saw what is hidden
inside that teddy bear
My husband is a police officer
- You know that, da?
- [thwacks]
[repeated bashing]
'Burn down the whole house'
Let her burn to ashes
along with the toy
[somber music]
[panic attack]
[flickers]
[fire blazing]
[howling]
[screaming]
AMMA!
'Amma'
'It's okay, child
Calm down'
- 'Everything is going to be alright'
- Don't let them escape, chitha
'Don't let them escape, chitha'
'DON'T LET THEM GO SCOT-FREE, CHITHA'
Vetri
[pulsating music]
[door screeches]
[pulsating music continues]
[violently kicks]
[glass shatters]
[pulsating music continues]
[suspenseful music builds]
[clanks]
- [pulsating music]
- [clicks]
[gasps]
[gun fires]
'Viji's fear phobia'
'Through M-M'
'Directed Thalapathy toward Himmler
who planned to control India'
I saw this same teddy in the News
'This teddy being the reason
for Viji's fear phobia'
'And the toys found in the ship'
'Thalapathy went
in search of the crucial link'
'Many items are in the ship
that was attacked'
Why are you asking
only about toys, madam?
For an important article, sir
[suspenseful music]
Company is J H Toys
'All the toys imported
for the past 15 years'
'Full details is in
this summary sheet'
[thrilling music]
[thrilling music continues]
[snaps fingers]
5 million toys
[thrilling music intensifies]
J H Toys
African Company
Throughout India
To specific toy shops
For 15 years
They have been
dispatching 5 million toys
Not 50 lakh toys
5 million guns!
[gripping music]
Take out the details
of all the shop-owners
[gripping music continues]
Toys Universe, Tamil Nadu
Kumaravel, Rajaram
Toys Boss, Karnataka
Heppe Gowda
Toys & Toys
U.P Bihar, Sagar
Wait... wait... wait
Tamil Nadu owners
Repeat their names
'Kumaravel, Rajaram'
Kovai Kumaravel?
'Yes'
Sendhai Rajaram?
Yes again
How do you know?
Your channel is operative
in all the States, right?
Yes
Call all the senior reporters
in all the States
[Kannada] How did you know about him?
[Telugu] How do you know, sir?
How are you so accurate?
Yes, you are right
Your information
is 101% right, sir
[Hindi] That's very, very, very dangerous
15 years ago
100% you are right
But do you know
who he is now?
[gripping music continues]
What are you doing?
What's going on?
All the toy shop owners
you gave me in your list
15 years ago, all of them were gangsters
who shook their respective States
'Uttar Pradesh
Gujarat'
'Rajasthan, Andhra Pradesh, Bihar'
'Delhi, Mumbai, Maharashtra'
[sharp music]
That isn't even the point
All of them now
Politicians
Dear people
Businessmen
Controllers of various institutions
'Big... big... big shots!'
[sharp music continues]
Unbelievable!
Who assembled all the gangsters
in India under one canopy?
How could all of them
become big shots?
'Could scientist Khaleel have
created such a big network?'
What do they intend doing
with 5 million guns?
There is something looming large
behind Viji's fear phobia
If we unravel that mystery
Not only can we solve Viji's problem
We can prevent the problem
that is about to swallow our motherland
- 'Long live
- Leader'
[shouting slogans]
[suspenseful music]
If we go now, we can
handover the file to CM
Okay
[suspenseful music continues]
So many strange things are
happening around me, Karthik
Chitha is being very aggressive
about me joining the military
'Did you talk to your dad?'
Viji
My dad is not like your uncle
It's my life
My wish, dear
I'll come over to your place
with my family tomorrow
'I love you'
Love you
Excuse me
Can you help me?
'What help?'
[suspenseful music continues]
You said you'll fix a date for
175th year jubilee of DGP building
- I said I'll attend
- Sir... sir
Apparently this is important, sir
- Then meet my bro-in-law
- No, sir
This spells danger
for your Govt it seems
This is a very important I believe
Please read it immediately, sir
[suspenseful music continues]
'Your file has come
to my own table in the end'
'Track that scientist Khaleel right away'
'Find out more about
that girl and kidnap her'
'Her name is Viji'
'Her paternal uncle is her guardian'
'We are #1 builders in Trichy'
We have assets worth
more than half a billion
'I wanted to pick a bride
from an affluent family'
He says he loves her
Girls nowadays sketch a plan and
pick the richest groom possible, right?
Only son, because of love failure
what if he commits suicide?
Iyer, please fix an auspicious date
- Won't you talk to the girl's unc-
- SHUT UP!
Poking your nose unnecessarily
Why are you quiet, man?
[ominous music]
No, sir
Viji has a lot to achieve in life
I don't want her to
get married immediately
You are talking as if
you are her biological dad
You just brought her up
That's all, right?
What will a girl
gain by achieving?
Get her married
My son will give her a son
Let her bring up my grandson
and be a dutiful wife and mother
'What... understood?'
[somber music]
[thrilling music builds]
Come, get up
- HEY!
- Sssshhhhhh!
What a wretched excuse
for a human you are!
Demeaning womenfolk like this?
One track mind, obsessed
with money, cash, rupees
Supposing I get my daughter
married to your son just like you asked
Supposing your son
died in a lorry accident
Your business tanked and
you ended up homeless, on the streets
What is the condition
of your family, hmmm?
My daughter will join
the army and win laurels
After that, if she still loves your son
Come to my doorstep then
You and your son can
live off her earnings
Shut your gob
and bugger off now
[heavily breathing]
'Karthik'
Karthik, wait please
I'll apologize
on behalf of my chitha
Please, sorry
Is he even human?
Behaving like an animal?
He isn't like that, Karthik
I can explain everything
Enough
We can decide about our love and
marriage later, focus on your future
If you are with him
none of your dreams will come true
First get rid of him, Viji
[emotional music]
Viji darling
Don't worry your pretty head
He is not the right choice for you, dear
When his dad spoke like that
he sat quiet without saying a word
He should support and say
you want to achieve, right?
First join the army-
Leave me alone, chitha
[sentimental music]
Go away from me
How does it matter to you
what I do with my life, chitha?
I don't want to join the army
I know it was my dream long ago
But I don't want that now
I want to get married
and lead a happy life
That's enough for me, chitha
Even now
I feel like yelling my throat hoarse to you
'leave me alone for God's sake'
But I don't have the guts to do so
Look how my hand is shaking
Viji
If my dad had been alive today
He would have at least felt sorry for me
and left me to do what I want
[sniffling]
Anxiety, fear, phobia
I am plagued with
so many weaknesses
How can I fare well in the army, chitha?
I am begging you with folded hands
Viji
Don't talk to me
Don't follow me
Leave me alone and go, chitha
Viji?
[heartwrenching music]
Let her do what she wants
It is not right to force your view
How can I let go, Kayal?
How can you let her be?
Didn't you hear what she said just now?
Fear, anxiety, phobia
She has all these weaknesses
You think this world will allow
such a child to live peacefully?
I am right next to her today
Tomorrow?
Shouldn't she learn to be gutsy
to protect herself?
She's just a kid, saying something
in the heat of the moment
Why should I take it to heart?
- [sniffles]
- [heartwrenching music continues]
Whatever happens, I cannot
give up on my child, Kayal
I will beg her
I will make her understand
If need be, I'll even fall at her feet
Her fear is the sole reason
It has created a hatred
over her goal in life
We must wipe out that fear
And make her strong
Like a tigress
I can do it
I will do it
[heartwrenching music continues]
My beautiful bud with nectar sweet
My child, like a red fish treat
Baffled & bewildered, cutie
Don't drift away from me
Scared and confused, my dear
Stay with me, I am always near
My child; mango flower scented
I stood clueless, torn and fragmented
Mixed up and muddled, sweetie
Don't walk away from me
Puzzled and panicked, baby
Stay close, don't leave me
[emotional music]
Bro, this is the house of
the girl who gave the file
[gate screeches]
[thunder rumbling]
[gripping music]
[screaming in panic]
'Run... save your skin'
Run for your life
Hey! Get in
Get into the car
- [gripping music]
- [thunder rumbles]
Anna! Why are your limbs
trembling in fear?
Petrified because of one man, huh?
You could've killed him there
and brought the girl over?
That would have been impossible
His hands shoved 30 lives to hell
And I witnessed it
in front of my eyes
NOT HEARD ABOUT HIM?
NOT HEARD ABOUT THALAPATHY'S
FULL-THROTTLE FRENZY?
BLOOD-SHED HUMAN SACRIFICE OF 30 LIVES
HE OFFERED THE FOREST DEITIES?
NOT HEARD ABOUT IT?
'In order to loot the minerals
worth millions found in this area'
'Evacuating the residents of
the hamlets here who were a hindrance'
'Fell on our leader's shoulders'
Don't spare a single soul
Round up everyone here
[slashing and stabbing]
'Hoist them up that tree'
'If the entire hamlet does not
evacuate this forest region'
We will burn down everyone
along with this tree
Even if we die,
we will not leave this land
Then you deserve to die
- [crowd wailing]
- [gut wrenching music]
[embers blazing]
[vicious laughter]
ANNAAAAAAA!
[metal clangs]
'The anguished screams
of the innocent people'
'The forest guarding deity
heard the cries loud and clear'
[mass music intensifies]
Hearing their loud wails
Whether Goddess Kali swirled Her trident
in a cosmic dance possessing him
Or their forest deity replicated
Shiva's dance of fury, we don't know
But listen
Every single strike he delivered
[mass music continues]
[thunder rumbles]
The trees that touched the skies
stood still in sheer panic
Witnessed a witch-hunt like never before
[mass music continues]
[continuous slashing]
- [mass music continues]
- [continuous slashing]
[mass music continues]
[screaming]
It instilled in me a terror
that will shake me till my last breath
He killed 30 men readily
for the forest people's sake
How many will he kill for his daughter?
Think about it
[ominous music]
As long as he is alive
We can't touch that girl
Divert attention
You were not their target, anna
They came for your daughter
Did they get a whiff
of our investigation?
'They even went to
her college in the morning'
Danger is circling her, anna
Anna, he is that girl's friend
Hi, bro
Advance
Viji, you are in danger
Allow me to be near you
- Viji, don't even talk to me
- Let's go
Let me just be
beside you, that's enough
Viji
Viji, Karthi wanted to
see you urgently
- Why?
- Don't know
Something important
it seems, come soon
[thrilling music]
Anna, why are you still waiting here?
Viji has already left
- What do you mean?
- Yes
Karthik wanted to see her urgently
She went with his friend a while ago
[thrilling music continues]
[mobile ringing]
Chitha is calling me
First switch off that phone
If he comes, he will create a ruckus again
[thrilling music continues]
'I will send you the # of a boy Suresh'
Track his live location
and text it to me
Suresh
You said Karthik called me
Why have you brought me here?
Who are they?
Vroom!
[screams]
Hi, bro, I brought the girl
following your instructions
Settle my balance account
Give, da
[sharp stab]
[thrilling music continues]
Account closed
Where is scientist Khaleel?
I don't even know him, anna
- [slaps]
- [shrieks]
[thrilling music continues]
After giving the file to Chief Minister
You are pretending to be ignorant?
He was handicapped
and I helped him
I don't know anything else
about him, anna
- [slaps]
- [shrills]
[thuds]
Last warning
If you don't divulge
Khaleel's whereabouts
I'll dice you to bits
'And throw you into the fire
ready to char you'
I've checked her phone fully
It has no information
about Khaleel
'Even his phone # isn't saved'
Doesn't seem like this girl is involved
She's innocent, sir
Innocent, huh?
Imbecile!
Would she have given the file
without seeing it?
Kill her
[heavily gasping]
- [heartbeat magnifies]
- [pulsating music]
[emotional music]
'Whenever you are
in trouble of any kind'
'Think of 'appa'
in your tiny heart'
'Wherever I am, I will
come rushing in front of you'
- [heart beating]
- [emotional music continues]
'Appa'
[bike whizzing]
[tense music building]
Son of King Ravana
Stand-alone Yama in the arena
Every reflection is his own
Ruler of the world; well-known
Come and strike if you dare
Blood will paint all over, mid-air
Who is the fool wanting to fight?
Our hero is the embodiment of light
He walks with a deadly lean
Every nerve coils tight and mean
Your blessed fate to be hit
Into a spin your crazy mind will split
Do you have the warrior-spirit?
Or hollow pride of unscaled summit?
Madness to provoke him, you moron
Is your face not yet swollen?
Sorry, chitha
You cautioned me
I disobeyed you
[softly sighs]
[gripping music]
[menacing chuckle]
They threatened to kill me
Huh?
[scornful chuckle]
Your chitha is here, right?
No one will dare
lay his finger on you
Get up
When you were a kid, what was
the fond nickname you had for me?
- Superman
- Hahn!
Even now in my bike
Whooooosh!
Like Superman
Good show, eh?
Anna, you said he will fight
with fury and frenzy?
Like a scaredy-cat
he is taking her away
[all laughing]
If you lock her in that iron cage
We are 60 of us here
Your daughter's death is confirmed
[thrilling music intensifies]
- [metal loudly clangs]
This day and date
Many years can come and go but today
will stick in your head like glue, da
I didn't want to witness
2 moments in my life
One is her eyes welling up with tears
Second is the fear of death
lurking in her eyes
'I had the misfortune
to witness both today'
You think I will
spare you that easily?
You would have heard about
the witch-hunt I led 20 years ago
You will witness it now
I want to know the hand
that raised to strike
I have to identify the mouth
that spat those words
Whoever sent you... that-
[metal clanks]
I want to know his name now
The one who snitches to me
will be spared from the jaws of death
And he will have a rebirth!
[mass music intensifies]
Whoever dies with this blow
will actually be blessed by this boon
By mistake he survives
His life will be sheer hell
Son of Ravana, born to command
Like Yama, he needs no second hand
He is the soul in every frame
The universe bows to his name
Come close enough to try
You will bleed before you die
Who dares stand against his might?
Our hero blazes, pure and bright
A deadly tilt in his stride
Power coiling in every nerve inside
Your fate is yours alone
One swift hit, your wits will be blown
Do you have the guts to fight?
Or false bravado without any might?
Madness to provoke him, you moron
Is your face not yet swollen?
A hero of flame; victory-star
Whoever defies, limbs will char
The moment his foes see his face
they will stand frozen in place
You could script his life as dialogue
He serves his foes an epilogue
His tale transcends every monologue
Send an enemy, he will simply smile
Who sent you to harass my daughter?
WHO IS THAT SCUMBAG?
Son of King Ravana
Stand-alone Death-lord Yama
Every reflection is his own
Leader of the universe; well-known
Come closer if you dare
You'll bleed to death, I swear
Who is the fool wanting to fight?
Our hero is the avatar of light
[upbeat thrilling music]
[wood breaks]
[upbeat thrilling music continues]
[continuous action]
[metal clangs]
That's girl's father barged in, boss
Hey! Are you narrating a story?
Close his chapter too
Kill him?
Imagine Goddess Kali possessing
the guardian deity's body?!
'He is hitting them
in a blaze of frenzy'
[continuous slashing]
Every blow is like a flash of lightning
piercing all our boys
[gripping music]
Show his face to me
[electrocution]
[mass music intensifies]
Hey Thalapathy
[mass music continues]
Hey! You told me
you had killed him in jail
I tried my best
I didn't succeed
If you get to know this
you'll get stressed
High Command stopped me
in case it creates a problem for M-M
[crashes]
[yelling]
CHITHAAA!
- [gripping music]
- [shrieking]
[yelling]
[metal clangs]
[villainous music]
[thwacks]
Uncs, help!
Speak up now
You made a grave blunder
involving my daughter in this
I will kill you, dice you
to bits and pieces-
'You already killed me and
went to jail for your crime'
'Did you forget that?'
'Thalapathy Vetri Kondan'
[villainous music intensifies]
'The Deputy Commissioner
Amrish Pujari you shot dead'
'Now'
The undying eternal one
Immortal John Himmler
Immortal John Himmler!
I wanna show you something
What?
Mortal terror of death!
[slashes]
Son of King Ravana
Stand-alone Death-lord Yama
He is the soul in every frame
Kill him
The universe bows to his name
Come and strike me if you dare
Blood will gush out in mid-air
Who is the bull that dares to fight?
Our hero is the light shining bright
Do not miss a single frame
He should be able to see my image
[sharp thud]
I need to see his terror-stricken face
[mass music]
[slashes]
[chops]
Son of Ravana, born to command
Like Yama, he needs no second hand
Every reflection is his own
Ruler of the world; well-known
Come and touch me if you dare
Blood will spurt for all I care
What, bro?
It's very wrong, bro
I don't care!
Son of King Ravana
Stand-alone Yama in the arena
Every reflection is his own
Global leader; well-known
Come and strike, if you dare
Blood will spew & splash everywhere
Who is the fool wanting to fight?
Our hero is the epitome of light
All these years
my daughter was scared stiff
Now you will be frightened to death
Thalapathy?
I am not that old DCP you knew
I am powerful enough to unseat
Presidents and Prime Ministers
John Himmler
You call yourself
by whatever name you like
Be ready to watch
Thalapathy's dance of fury
[snickering]
Last warning
Don't butt in here
claiming to be a Good Samaritan!
Save your skin
Scoot from here
'I will close your chapter'
'I will disgrace you'
Anyone can make such tall claims
I have no intention
of turning my back
I am
[dismissive tongue-click]
Coming!
One name spells history
No force can erase his story
He is our savior
People's favorite leader
[heavy downpour]
'The feud between
Thalapathy and Himmler'
'It isn't a personal vendetta'
'That is a movement
to protect democracy'
'Madurai
2005'
[parai drum beats]
- Come with me, man
- Wait, uncle
Hey Kasi, pour 2 glasses
No need, uncle
My wife will yell at me
Go on, drink
I'll take care of you, drink
[slurring]
[suspenseful music]
My dear!
What happened?
I drank hooch
My chest is on fire!
I can't see properly
'Aiyo!'
APPA!
[suspenseful music continues]
[crowd wailing]
Doctor... doctor
Doctor, come and check please
He isn't breathing, doctor
He's gone
#52, enter casualty count
Why did you do this?
- 59, 60...61
- What is this, doctor?
Death toll exceeding 60
62 - 63
[woman sobbing]
HEY!
CLAIM YOUR DEAD
AND VACATE THIS PLACE
When my son asks, 'where is my appa?'
will you reply on my behalf?
Till you arrest the illicit liquor peddlers
I won't claim my husband's body
Yes, we won't either
Arrest the scums
Arrest the scumbags!
Arrest the rascals
Arrest the scoundrels!
Sir?
I'll do as you say
Okay, sir
[protesting with slogans loudly]
HEY!
LAST WARNING
FOR EVERYONE
Better claim the body and leave
Or we will burn them for you
Try to lay a hand
on my husband
Try your luck!
Lift the body
of your loved one
Let us protest in front of
the commissioner's office
- Till we get due justice
- Lift
Arrest the thugs
Arrest the scumbags!
'Govt Hospital, Madurai'
[shouting aloud slogans]
Sir, the issue is
out of proportion
'Arrest the culprits immediately'
'Don't let them go scot-free!'
Sir, it may boomerang on us
'Arrest the heartless rascals!'
'Arrest them
We want justice!'
'Let truth rise above this'
Arrest the criminals
Punish the immoral
Let truth rise above this
We demand justice
Arrest the culpri-
[continuous bashing]
[crowd protesting]
[thrilling music]
'Mob has started
getting violent, sir'
FIRE!
- [gun fires]
- Arrest the crimin-
[open fire]
[crowd shrieking]
[continuous gunfire]
[tense music brooding]
'Police opened fire
on protestors of illicit liquor'
'Opposition condemns the police firing'
[thrilling music erupting]
Illicit liquor peddlers
who caused my husband's death
Police who killed the protestors
I will not leave this spot
till these offenders are arrested
'Holding ground in front of Kannagi statue
demanding justice for her husband's death'
'A bold Porkodi
protests against all odds'
'People's support to the protest amplifies'
'Bullets the prize
for voice of justice?!'
'Chief Minister orders transfer of
all senior officials in Madurai district'
'IAS topper Leela Rani
appointed as District Collector'
'IPS topper Amrish Pujari'
'Appointed as new
Deputy Commissioner of Police'
'Ready to risk my life
to ensure people's safety'
'DC Amrish Pujari's sensational interview'
Aren't you ashamed
to wear this uniform?
In this district alone
You couldn't even nab
those who brewed the illicit liquor
Why?
Is someone holding you back?
I WANT TO KNOW THE REASON
'Sir'
Hey! Won't you shut your gob?
I will tell you, sir
Go in and see for yourself, sir
'You will identify the offender'
[ominous music]
'Roja Rangaswamy'
That name doesn't feature
only in that file, sir
'It will be written
on every file you see here'
[sinister music]
Not just illicit liquor, sir
'Marijuana, kangaroo court
with palm-greasing'
Granite quarry, sand mafia
Murder, loot, contracts
All anti-social, criminal,
filthy activities are organized by
The untouchable
The one and only
Undefeated Roja Rangaswamy
[sinister music intensifies]
A powerful politician
even the CM is scared of, sir
[sinister music continues]
Hello
District Secretary of the Ruling Party
Roja Rangaswamy speaking
Regarding?
'Regarding' means what, da?!
- About what?
- Oh!
About whether you want to be alive or not
Your kind information, you're talking
to the Deputy Commissioner of Police
I have written some laws
just like Ambedkar's code of law
Roja Rangaswamy Law Code
'According to my laws'
You should meet me
before you check files in your office
First salute is for me
Do that and go
I will come
I'll beat you to a pulp
Strip your shirt off
and parade you in your knickers
PREPARE FORCE
ASSEMBLE COMPLETE FORCE THERE
[pulsating music]
SURROUND THE BUILDING
No one should exit
No one should enter
[pulsating music continues]
Get up, man
[mocking laughter in unison]
[ominous music]
SIR!
[crowd clamor]
'Sir, no clue how and where
they sprouted like mushrooms from'
1000 people around the house
10,000 all around the road
'In this entire area'
'More than 100,000
have encircled us, sir'
- [dramatic music intensifies]
- [crowd clamor]
The moment you entered the Record Room
my men surrounded me to protect me
Look
[ominous music]
Hey!
If you have to strip me half naked
You need authority
And power
That rests
In the palm of my hand
[slaps]
[ominous music continues]
- [fabric ripping]
- [haunting emotional music]
- [haunting emotional music continues]
[haunting emotional music continues]
[taunting laughter]
[fabric ripping]
Hey!
Who made you DC, eh?
You studied, strived hard for this post
You passed in flying colors
and became Deputy Commissioner
But I, on the other hand
1 million people voted for me and
I'm elected representative of the people
District Secretary of a Party
with millions of members
Not merely a district official
We belong to a dynasty of rulers
Officers like you are
always lone wolves
But politicians
Always move in a pack!
Hey!
Bring it here
Toe the line at least from now on
Wear this and go
with your dignity intact
[haunting emotional music continues]
[derisive choral laughter]
[mortified music]
Sir...?
You're asking questions
of no consequence
We placed a bet in a game
He won
[ridiculing laughter]
'3rd consecutive day
of hunger-strike'
'Roja Rangaswamy claims
it is Opposition's deliberate ploy'
'College students showed solidarity
by wearing black badge'
'School students distributed notice
advocating their support for the protest'
Brother, this is Porkodi's daughter
- Ask your appa to support us
- Okay, akka
'Selvi?'
Yes, anna
AMMA!
[gripping music]
'Arrest the culprit, pin down
the cops who abetted the crime'
1 hour time
If you don't get up
Like you got to see her uniform
You won't see your daughter
Put an end to your protest and disperse
[gripping music continues]
[patriotic music]
It is not my daughter's dignity
fluttering in the wind
The honor of our nation
'On the ruling Party's flag post'
'School girl's uniform flutters
in defiance of authority'
'Modern Kannagi's demand for justice'
'Viral video of Porkodi's uniform'
'Women's Associations demanding
the arrest of Roja Rangaswamy immediately'
Leader, watching all this
don't resort to drastic actions
Then your Party won't exist in 6 districts
That woman's hunger-strike
is causing ripples now, man
Come on, sir
'I can handle that with ease'
[fire blazing]
[crowd shrieking]
'Sir, Roja's men have landed there'
'Do something, sir'
What is this fat file?
[shrieks]
[slaps]
Inspector by name Thalapathy
He has massacred 30 people because
they roughed up villagers in a hamlet, sir
Have you arrested him?
Owning up to the crime
5000 residents of those hamlets
are ready to surrender, sir
Then what action did you take?
We have meted out
a different punishment, sir
[screaming in pain]
[shrilling]
What punishment?
Transfer, sir
Where to?
[amused laughter]
[gloating laughter]
AMMA!
[knife whooshing]
[metal clanging]
[mass music erupts]
[mass music continues]
'The fuse is lit wild in my eyes'
'Yeah'
'The cries echo to great heights'
'Every plan to escape,
you thought that you could'
'It's Game Over, homie
when law hails down your hood'
'Know that, long as I'm here
I brute you the guilt'
'I wield the Sword of Justice
tearin' up the filth'
'Look her a wrong way
grave with your name'
'Disrespect women
calls garlands on your frame'
'Catch you goin' adrift,
single mistake'
'Consequence to a woman's peril's lethal,
I unleash them swift'
'The fuse is lit wild in my eyes'
'Yeah'
'The cries echo to great heights'
'People's trust in the uniform's fabric'
'Standin' here through
the love of the people'
'No mercy for the crooks, servin' savage'
'Law ain't partial
To everyone equal'
'Close a pending case
and I'm on the next major sequel'
'Castin' brighter lights,
wardin' off all the evil'
'See you slippin', I may go
the lengths to seize you'
'Got more convicts in the cell
than you knew before'
Sir, this knife slipped by mistake
and slashed the neck
5-6 heads got hacked, sir
I am surrendering, sir
As soon as an issue crops up
self immolation, hunger-strikes
They don't get you anywhere
An eye for an eye
Payback in equal measure
First eat properly
Let my daughter come
I will eat then
She will come
Eat now
[phone ringing]
Go
'Go and speak'
Listening to his voice
your voice will change
'Your body will shake and shiver'
He will order you to shoot me
Obey his order, go now
Inspector speaking
I made your DC run in disgrace
with just his shorts on
You won't even have that luxury!
[sniffles]
Ask for a glass of water
next to your chair
- Why?
- You'll need it, ask
Get me a glass of water, da
Done
What do you want to stir?
'SIR!'
Thalapathy
He has sent heads, sir
[mass music erupts]
[mass music continues]
If Porkodi's daughter does not
come here right now
With hundredfold more enmity
than her mother to seek vengeance
I will come there
Your entire empire
The girl will get home
[car whirring]
[door opens]
HEYYY!
AIYO!
Oh gawd!
Selvi
Sir... sir... sir
'You thought I got scared?'
[jeering laughter]
[tense music]
I am hosting a feast tomorrow at home
'Both of you should
definitely come over'
News should carry videos of you feasting
with a smile plastered on your faces
If that doesn't happen
'You saw that girl's body stripped naked'
Tomorrow you may have to see
your mother's body in the same state
'After that'
I may have to see your lifeless body!
[angry grunt]
Ask for the feast to be prepared
[crowd erupts in cheers]
[whistles and cheers]
THALAIVAA!
All of you, enjoy the feast
and only then leave
[crowd erupts in cheers]
[whistles and cheers]
[screams]
[heavy thud]
[drumbeats grow louder]
Come, my dear... welcome!
Eat
[camera shutters snap]
Thalapathy
My family has been immersed
in politics for 50 years!
'My grandfather'
My father
Now it's me
Tomorrow, my son
My grandson
We will continue our politics
Our word will be law
Knowing all this,
I swear you-
[pulse-pounding music]
[amused laughter]
If you want another husband, ask me
I'll send over some fellow
Instead of that, what's this
protest, hoisting a flag?!
[sadistic laughter]
If she had co-operated
she will be alive today, no?
Nothing much
Her daughter acted pricey
She died because of a few tight slaps
This rascal!
[raunchy laughter]
[blade pierces flesh]
Son of Ravana, born to command
Like Yama, he needs no second hand
You are narrating a story seriously
he's laughing his head off!
Stup-id!
Come closer if you dare
You'll bleed to death, I swear
Kindly continue, sir
HEY!
- What the ef-
- HEY!
[loud slap]
HEY! He assaulted our leader
Don't let a single policeman step out alive
[crowd erupts]
[sounds of fighting]
[music swells heroically]
[shrill whistle]
[loud scream]
[whistle]
[heroic music]
[music soars]
[rapid gunfire]
'CLOSE THE GATE'
NONE OF YOU SHOULD MOVE AN INCH
You can leave only after
you watch what unfolds now
Hey! Open the door
'My precious gem Thalapathy'
[wind whooshes]
[triumphant music]
Thala...!
Hey! Open, quick!
Listen
You are acting with no idea
of the repercussions
For one who didn't
follow Indian Law
My Law will apply from now
[loud yell]
[rope whips through the air]
"If I command, it happens then and there"
"The poor won't sink in tears of despair"
[whistling]
Did you hear the sound?
That plush seat of power you occupy by
duping the public and slouching in idleness
Hey... hey!
'Will burn to cinders'
Your seat of power will break
and shatter to bits
[shatters]
[heroic music]
Our precious gem most worthy
Blast
Blast!
[victorious music]
Blessing and grace of
each and every Tamil woman
...will accompany you
wherever you go, sir
This is a promise
One name etched in history
No force can erase his story
He is the bold redeemer
People's elected leader
Without people thinking twice
no change can be made otherwise
He came to deliver
A man of substance forever
Hearing your name all around
hearts and minds freeze, spell bound
On our eye-screen, lifted sky-high
you'll always be the apple of our eye
If you stand as Rock of Gibraltar
a whole race will survive longer
If you move far away
our lives will go astray
Now on, I fight this battle for all of you
Beat of my heart, blood, breath so true
As your soldier I will march by your side
Always in my heart, you will all reside
This blade's story
gleams in timeless glory
I will continue to fight
with all my might
As long as he's on the battlefield
fate of his frightened foes is sealed
One name spells history
I have arrived!
Hereafter the looting by sand mafia
Brewing illicit liquor
Corruption, bribery, caste-bias
Put an end to all these offenses right now
Hereafter my words
won't convey my intentions
My actions will speak
I'll dice all of you
Throw en masse
to float in the river
Beware!
[victorious upbeat music]
His fury makes him sleepless
His flag will fly high ageless
He never bows his head
The storm retreats instead
In Time's phases three
he is beyond compare truly
His fame will never wane away
A lion will never become a prey
When you go wherever
garlands will seek you forever
As heavy sighs of sadness we heave
our eyes will grieve rain to see you leave
The joy you've given glows world over
Time for us to thank you, people's leader
Our hearts will hold you every day
as our dream come true forever to stay
This battle I fight for every one of you
My heartbeat, blood, pulse & breath anew
As your soldier I will march by your side
Always in my heart, you will all reside
This sword's story
gleams in timeless glory
I will fight with all my might
Soldier by day and night
As long as he is on the battlefield
fate of his frightened foes is sealed
One name rewrites history
No force can erase his story
He is the savior
Democratic leader
[loud wail of despair]
[screams of despair echo]
DC seems deeply disturbed, ma'am
Better to break down the door
and start treatment at once
[music grows tense]
Putting up with this humiliation
Why am I still alive?
Die
Better die
DIE
Better off dying
[screams]
Why am I living?
DIE
DON'T LIVE, DIE
[heavy, angry breathing]
Who... who is that?
Who prevented me from dying?
('Why should you die?')
Then what?
You want me to be humiliated
Lose my authority and
be a slave to bureaucracy?
('Is that your fault?')
('Are you to blame?')
Don't you understand?
Come here
Come in front of me
Look... look at this
Look, 10 years ago
'He was a drug peddler'
'Today he's a councilor'
This chap...15 years ago, he was
conducting full-on kangaroo court
Today he's a chairman
This lowlife vagabond
heads the sand mafia
Today he is a politician MLA
All of them are controlled by
the Ruling Party's District Secretary
Wanting to clean up
our nation of corruption
We arrest such criminals,
and put them behind bars
But these people
This ignorant public
Vote for the same criminals we arrested,
crowning them with title and position
'Ensure they occupy seats of power'
What's even more demeaning, we have
to salute the same criminals we arrested!
Salute, sir
Salute!
Not only here
Whole of India
Same sad plight
I cannot live stomaching this disgrace,
without authority and as a slave
Give me my gun
I WANT MY GUN
COME OUT
COME OUT!
[ominous music]
Hey!
Who are you?
You are ME, da
You won't be a slave
to anyone any longer
Entire Tamil Nadu will become your slave!
How?
You don't need this
slave of a policeman's job
Become a politician
Grab authority into your hands
Who will vote for me?
If an illiterate imbecile like Roja
'Can deceive the people
into voting for him'
An educated police officer like you
Imagine how easily you can con them
and bulk up your vote bank?
How can I do this single handed?
Follow the footsteps of
Hitler and the British
Divide them on the basis of caste,
community, region, religion, language
Incite rebellion and unrest
Let the people die in their own in-fighting
Enforce controlled democracy
This is atrocious
The people will bear the brunt of it
Didn't you tell me just now?
The people ruined our country by
voting the wrong candidates to power
Then who are the real criminals?
Huh?
People
NO...I DON'T AGREE
- WRONG
- RIGHT
It is wrong
Not wrong... not wrong at all
WRONG, I WON'T AGREE
Will you obey me or not?
NO, I WON'T
YOU DESERVE TO DIE THEN
DIE
- It's a crime
- THEN DIE
'Wrong'
[rapid gunfire]
[eerie music]
[labored breathing]
[loud knock on door]
[dark, heroic music]
'Sir'
Roja has been arrested
Wear your uniform again
with your usual swag, sir
There is no authority
labelled on this uniform
The uniform I will wear hereafter
Completely different!
[upbeat tense music]
'Don't be scared'
'Don't think I want to take revenge on you'
I am not such an idiot!
Shake hands
I have humiliated you
I don't have any power, position, Party
Why are you here?
Why do you need a Party or position?
You will start a new independent Party
I intend to
Make you win the election
and become the Chief Minister
You will make me Deputy CM
I don't understand
But first suggest anything to
kill Thalapathy who sent me to this hell
I'll do it
Wherever I turn
People are celebrating him
If you kill him now
he will become God!
Kill him without making him a martyr
'Shall I tell you my plan?'
[dark, upbeat music]
Hey!
What?
I want to meet Thalapathy sir
Very important matter
He has taken off for 2 days
to attend a temple festival
[lively folk music]
SIR
My name is Ilias, sir
'I was given an order to make
40 color bombs for a school function, sir'
'When we were doing it'
What is this?
Gelatin, RDX are being unloaded?
Ilias
You are doing this for God
You should just zip your lips
If you pack this much explosive
Do you realize the death toll, bhai?
[thrilling music]
Let them die
I wanted to convey this
I went to meet the Deputy Commissioner, sir
Hey!
[music grows tense]
[intense, rhythmic music]
[bomb explodes]
[multiple explosions]
[haunting, somber music]
'Oh my God!'
Aiyo! My dear
[tense music]
'Religious riots follow the bomb blasts
with Al-Rah owning responsibility'
'Ruling party has failed in its duty to
protect the people from terrorist attack'
'Roja Rangaswamy plans to launch
a new Party dedicated to people's welfare'
'In the coming election,
contesting in all 234 constituencies'
'He vows to topple the ruling party'
[intense music]
WHY?
WHY, DA?
SO MANY INNOCENT LIVES!
Let them die
This is... just the beginning
NO
Wait
Waaait!
Listen fully to my plan of action
Then get angry
Hereafter riots will spread
throughout Tamil Nadu
People who vote according to
their caste and religious preference
They will vote for us instead
Our Party will win the election
We will rule with power in our hands
I will control the whole of Tamil Nadu
Dai... dai... DAI!
You are thinking
in a villainous way
Me...?
AM I WRONG?
Securing a job in a reputable firm means
being grilled with endless questions
'What is his vision?
Is he educated?'
'Is he experienced?
How is his character?'
But to vote
No questions asked
Candidate is our religion
Vote for him, don't think twice
He is our caste, vote for him
Our symbol, vote for him
I am not the fool, da
People are the fools, da
One who brands the people as fools
is the worst fool ever!
Son of an ordinary laborer
How did you join the police force?
The certainty that only by
good actions can one win votes
Gave the illiterate education,
shelter and self worth
Some may vote without thinking straight
Only we have to get
to brass tacks and change them
Those who tried to change people
have lost the game
We must use their foolishness
to our advantage
Even if you want to do good, it can
be done only by choosing the wrong path
REVOLUTION OF MY MIND
IS RIGHT
Because of one disgrace
one single event
Your mind change
That's not revolution, da
REVENGE!
CHANGE IS A PROCESS
It will take time
It will be slow
You will never understand my theory
[gunfire]
SIR?
ILIAS!
[grunts and blows]
YOU
You didn't take the IPS exam
intending to serve the people, da
It was power-fueled fury
that spurred you to become a cop
He's a terrorist
ARREST THEM!
'Both of them planted a bomb'
YOU SHOULDN'T EVEN BE ALIVE, DA
[gunfire]
Madam, your son has been
in touch with terrorists
He has killed the DC who exposed him
Is it true he had stashed
weapons in your house?
YES
[melancholy music]
You abandoned these people
who supported you
Why did you stick to my side, chitha?
Viji dear
Do you remember what you told me
when you were very young?
You said you were my mother
Will anyone abandon their mother
when she is in trouble?
[heartfelt music]
I will listen to whatever
you tell me hereafter
[heartfelt music]
[zipper closes]
As per his plan, Roja secured 3rd place
with his newly formed Independent Party
But if his plan was to rule the State
Why distribute weapons
throughout India?
Who funded him to
purchase all these weapons?
The very thought terrifies me
I think we should first
contact the central agencies
What will you say
if they ask for evidence?
Himmler is planning something
with his dangerous ideology
We have to find out
his entire strategy
'Till then, we need a Safe House
where we cannot be traced'
'The right place for it'
'Military Training Campus'
How can we enter that campus?
Using Viji's training
to our advantage
FASTER
[rapid footsteps]
'FASTER...UP'
FASTER...UP
Good morning, Major
We have rejected
your daughter's application
'So what brings you here?'
No, I was told she can clear
the Army test if you train her
'That's why
Please, Major'
Many girls will come and join
Eager beavers at first like this
Just 2 days
They will run away
saying it was too tough
Girls are only fit to take on jobs
free of physical strain
Cinema modeling, all that is fine
'Not for army'
They lack that strength
You are completely wrong, sir
Are there no women in our army?
You think I am wrong?
WOMEN ARE WEAK!
Should I prove you?
PUT YOUR BAG DOWN
RUN
Faster
[tense music intensifies]
I SAID 'FASTER'
'Faster'
'FASTER'
She couldn't run
even 3 rounds in 1 minute
You want to see more?
'I will show you more'
On the floor
ON THE FLOOR
DO PUSH UPS
'START, 1'
Two
'THREE'
She couldn't even make it to 10 push-ups
'She is shivering'
'You had the gall to say
I am wrong, huh?'
You want to see more?
YOU, INSIDE THE RING
[music grows tense]
- Suraj?
- Sir
He is my Academy's best student
He will show you
a final demo now
'Suraj'
- Kick her out
- She's not at all trained
That too, how can she hit a boy?
You think she can hit him?
'No chance for all that'
At least let us watch if she has
the strength to bear one single blow
Suraj
Yes, sir
[suspenseful music intensifies]
[fists thud and grunts]
One more blow from me, she will die
Take your girl back
'Teach her how to cook, draw 'kolam'
and make sure she learns properly'
'Get her married to someone'
- That can be done, sir
- Huh?
[heroic music intensifies]
[fists thud and grunts]
Best student?
Oh! I forgot
He's a man
Let me give him another chance!
[struggling and grunting]
If you want me to teach
culinary skills to my daughter
Then what will you teach him?
What, bro?
It's a very wrong, bro!
You seem to be talented, but-
Very, very narrow minded
I know what to do
Come, Viji
Sir, he bought chocolate for this child
and sexually abused her
Rascal!
Take him to the station
Kayal
Take the child from him
[foreboding music]
Does he give you a candy
daily like this, baby?
[pained sigh]
Touching you like that is wrong
Haven't you been taught
at home or in school?
WHERE IS THIS CHILD'S SCHOOL?'
'Within this campus, sir'
Hi, everyone
I warmly welcome the principal
Most favorable parents
And teachers to this 75th Annual Day
- What happened, sir?
- Kayal
1 minute
[haunting, somber music]
My dear 'kutties'
'Nanbis'
'Uncle wants to share with you
a very important lesson'
Will all of you listen carefully?
[unified voices in assent]
Louder
[louder chorus agreeing]
Even LOUDER
[ROARING in agreement]
Some men will play with you
'Lure you with candies and
touch your body inappropriately'
You have to be very careful then
If he touches 3 parts of your body
it is very wrong, it is a crime
Whoever touches you like that
You must immediately
run and tell your mother
One is chest
Whoever touches you here
You should tell your amma
2nd is below your hip, back
If you are touched here
Tell your amma
3rd is between the legs
If touched there
it is a major crime
Run at once and tell your amma
The person who touches you
in these 3 parts
Maybe your friend who plays with you
Your teacher
Your neighbor uncle
Even in our own home
Your grandfather, uncle,
elder brother, younger brother
Even if he is your dad's elder brother
Tell your mother
Your mother won't keep quiet
Your mother should NOT ignore it
I was born and
brought up in a forest
I know to differentiate
a fox from a tiger clearly
But here
There can be a fox
disguised as deer
And wolf that wanders along with the fox
You should be safe, kiddos
An animal can never become a human
even if it tries very hard to do so
But a man can become a beast
The moment he sees a girl!
Hereafter, just keeping
a pepper spray in your bag
If something happens
lighting a candle in silent protest
'Don't resort to all that'
A girl should be brought up to
beat that 'beast' and skin him alive
Raise them strong
like a tigress
You can scale Mt Everest and still
They will demean you saying
'women are weak'
[uplifting music]
Stupid fellows!
He wouldn't have seen his mother suffer
labor pains when she gave birth to him
If he had watched
he would have realized
The strength of a woman
This lesson is more important
than anything else you teach
Teach this daily
In another year, your daughter
will be a military officer
I say it most respectfully
[triumphant music]
[upbeat, rousing music]
'Come on'
This is the Defense Radio Room
with direct satellite network you wanted
Kayal
Start your work
'Come on... come on'
'The fuse is lit wild in my eyes'
'Yeah'
'The cries echo to great heights'
'Every plan to escape,
you thought that you could'
'It's Game over, homie when law
hails down your hood'
'Know that, long as I'm here
I brute you the guilt'
'I wield the Sword of justice
tearin' up the filth'
'Look her a wrong way
grave with your name'
'Disrespect women
calls garlands on your frame'
'Catch you goin' adrift, single mistake,
consequence to a woman's peril's lethal'
'I unleash them swift'
'Pit you vs me in a brawl,
they know I'm the OG winner'
'Your people scatterin'
at the glimpse of the justice bringer'
'Another crook in chains, yeah
I'm steppin' up to the next level'
'In my radius, the badge
sendin' you felons to the devil'
[energetic rap music]
'Complying to Thalapthy's request'
'Kayal extracted all the details
of people in Himmler's network, A to Z'
'She showed an even more
important evidence to Thalapathy'
[tense music intensifies]
Look at the Navy officer's hand
M - M
That means?
'At the same time'
'DC followed Khaleel's wife'
'And kidnapped the scientist'
'He was tortured to reveal the hideout
of the evidence and modern weapons'
'Himmler found a crooked short-cut
to capture Thalapathy'
Go
[heavy blow lands]
[panic attack]
See, there's no space for you
to get anxious and panic
Physically she is perfect
But mentally
Her fear phobia is
making her step bac-
She will conquer it, sir
When you get a gap
to attack, use it then
Hey Viji
How come you are here?
- Hi
- Hey!
Only now she is focused in her training
- Don't disturb her
- Sir, I just want to talk to Viji
I'm asking you not to, right?
I want to talk to her just once, sir
'Chitha'
Let me handle him
Karthik, come... come
[ominous music builds]
Sit down
Sit... sit
I have set up a start-up company
It's huge
Oh!
What is this army stuff?
No need all this
You can't do this
Come with me
We can get married
and let's enjoy our life
[poignant music]
Unlike you, I won't discourage you
All the best
Are you mad or what?
You want to fall into
his trap once again?
He is playing with your life
He's a sadist
Sit down
Sit... sit
What did you say?
He has trapped me?
He's playing with my life?
Do you know the meaning
of 'sacrifice', da?
Leaving your business
Polishing my shoes
Making a glass of juice for me
Can you stand behind me
at least for 1 hour?
That man for 12 long years
He left his life, future, everything behind
and stood like a solid pillar for me
He put up with my tantrums
He tolerated being humiliated
He will smile when I smile
If I cry he will be heart-broken
He will always call me
'Viji dear' loaded with love
Who will do all this, da?
He will teach how a girl should stand with
courage and confidence in the world's eyes
I am standing
For his sake
I don't care if I lose my life doing so
And then... what did you say?
Sadist, huh?
He is my Thalapathy, da
My forever friend
My elder brother
My dad's younger brother
My 'appa' even if he is
not my biological dad
Even if you tell me to go away
I will not leave you; no way
Even if you turn into a fiery red flame
I won't burn in your anger all the same
Even if Time urges me to go to bed
I will be wide awake instead
Apple of my eye, my precious gem
'Vetri'
I will wait for you (im)patiently, come
My beautiful bud with nectar sweet
I've hassled her to follow her dream
from when she was a kid
I thought, in one corner of her mind,
she maybe angry with me
[warm music]
You heard her, Kayal?
I am
She said I am her 'appa'
This is enough for me, Kayal
One more step
All we need to do is
make Viji climb 1 step higher
Fear is the only barrier for her to do so
The fear he gave Viji and
the people of our country
We must destroy that fear
First we have to destroy him
'What is M-M?'
'To find out Himmler's whereabouts'
'To uproot his network'
'Thalapathy came up with a solid plan'
'Himmler sketched his own plan
to capture Thalapathy'
I know how to bring him out
Ask Roja to enter the forest
with 500 of his men
Tell him to kill the residents
of that entire mountain-forest
He will show up
[driving, tense music]
HEY!
Get them all, men, women,
children, the entire lot
[screams and commotion]
'Anna'
'Anna
Anna!'
Missing, anna
- Who is missing?
- The entire clan!
Move
Anna...!
Only one female is sitting
in front of the guardian deity
[distant thunder rumbles]
Oye!
Where is everyone?
WHERE?
Tel-
Burn her
[menacing inhale]
Will you tell me
or be ready to die?
Strip her and burn her naked, da
[cloth rips]
[tense music intensifies]
Take this glass of water
You will need it, take it
HEY! HE IS HERE
Go into the forest
and look for him
[tense music intensifies]
[scuffling and grunting]
[rapid gunfire]
[crowd erupts]
HEY!
Didn't you ask for Thalapathy?
He is coming for you
blazing in red hot fury
Son of King Ravana
Stand-alone Death-Lord Yama
Every reflection is his own
Ruler of the world; well-known
Come and touch me if you dare
Blood will spurt for all I care
Who is the fool that dares to fight?
Our hero is the embodiment of light
His strong stride has a deadly tilt
Power in every nerve to the hilt
Son of Ravana, born to command
Like Yama, he needs no second hand
Strong and mighty
Son of Ravana is he
'If Roja squeals
we will all be in a royal mess'
'How could you have been so careless?'
'We have worked for this
for 15 long years'
'How will M-M function now?'
M-M will definitely happen
'No one on earth can prevent this'
"If I command, it happens then and there"
[song from 'Enga Veetu Pillai']
"If it is well executed altogether"
"Some chase desire, suck up for their need
Some sweet-talk to satisfy their greed"
"No shame in their behavior"
"No self worth whatsoever"
"They grab the tail and blindly tread
Following paths where reason has fled"
"The future will dawn
My duty will begin then on"
"I will surely wipe out
this gang's misdeeds no doubt"
Instead of entering politics
to serve the people selflessly
Do you barge into politics
to loot and kill innocent lives?
[rope lashes]
What is M-M?
What do you plan to do
with so many guns?
Hey... hey... hey!
I knew you will come to me next
I'll tell you
From A to Z
But you cannot prevent it
Nor can you prove
we are the offenders
Because the culprits are the people
They will continue
to be the culprits!
[rapid gunfire]
'The day you shot our DC'
Shahul who planted a bomb for us
Thalapathy's men handed him
over to the police
'Police will be here anytime to arrest you'
Only if I am alive!
'We faked DC's death and
planted guns in your house'
'We threatened your mother and
forced her to make a false statement'
'And then, with help
from my arms suppliers'
'I facilitated DC's escape to Africa'
[tense music]
'At that time civil war was
rampant throughout Africa'
'Companies were exploiting
natural resources worth billions'
'But the President of Swasnia alone
was preventing entry of any company'
'DC discovered this and
approached all the companies'
'Signed an agreement stating
he can conquer Swasnia and provide entry'
'He entered Swasnia'
'He started toy factories slowly
and steadily within Swasnia'
'And smuggled guns
through those toys'
'He established caste and
religious institutions within Swasnia'
'Using those organizations as tools'
'My caste is higher
My religion is superior'
'He sowed seeds of hatred
in people's minds'
'That hatred flared day by day
in unreasonable proportions'
'It exploded into rebellion'
'Correctly at that point in time'
'He distributed freely to the people
guns smuggled by him in the toy factories'
'Civil war erupted'
[explosions and gunfire]
'People shot one another in a frenzy
driven by caste and religious hatred'
'Millions of people died'
[haunting vocalizations]
'Swasnia surrendered
at the feet of the companies'
'Companies started referring DC
as 'Man of Death' John Himmler'
India too has many differences like Africa
Caste, religion, language
State, north, south
If we execute this plan
Like Africa
India will be at our feet
[tense music]
M-M?
Mission Meluha
Meluha is
The name for Ancient India
Name of My India!
'First Stage of M-M'
'Store guns in India
just like we did in Africa'
'We started Hindu, Islamic and Christian
religious institutions all over the State'
'We set up IT wings, war rooms'
'Claiming we are superior
and they are an inferior lot'
'We spread many historic lies
on social media and WhatsApp'
'Not realizing hatred is
the strongest weapon in the world'
'People bought our stories'
Now is the final strike
Weapons
Guns
As soon as these arms
reach the people's hands
Similar to Africa
Civil war will explode in India
People's right to vote
will be revoked
Autocracy will bloom and blossom
Absolute authority will
fall into our hands
[tense music intensifies]
You think Indians too will
take to guns like Africans?
Are we Indians that stupid?
People won't take guns in their hands
We will be the ones shooting at them
'When we shoot'
People stemmed by hatred will support us
People of that religion
should be shot like this
People of that caste
should be hacked like this
Same with people of that State
People will voice their dissent
Last strike
Where and when is it happening?
Today
One hour from now
Many countries waiting to loot India
are supporting Himmler
You cannot do any damn heroism
Move aside
[tense music intensifies]
'Police Head Quarters
Chennai'
'Entire Tamil Nadu is safe guarded
by our diligent police department'
'Today is the reopening ceremony
of the DGP office after renovation'
'With immense pride Honorable Governor
and I are here for this special occasion'
'This building boasts of
a history of 175 years'
'Looking back with pride on that history'
'Many proud moments, sacrifices-'
[tense music intensifies]
'Stop... stop'
[tires squeal]
'I consider it my duty to
preside over this momentous occasion'
[alarm wails]
[bomb explodes]
[continuous explosions] [sustained gunfire]
[chaos erupts]
[menacing upbeat music]
Hi dummies
'Pakistan terrorists who seized control
of DGP's office in Tamil Nadu'
All the VIPs of this State
are my hostages
Who will run the State?
Whom should I talk to?
I am Leela Rani
Chief Secretary of Tamil Nadu
I am going to run the State
Chief Minister, Governor,
Deputy General of Police, Commissioner
If you want all of them alive
3 demands
1st demand
Whatever happens till dawn
No policeman should step out
of any station all over the State
TV and mobile signals should not be cut
- Not possible
- Make it possible
'Pcccht!'
'Prime Minister's instruction
not to accede to the terrorists' demands'
[Hindi] Go... go
'Armed forces are being deployed'
'Prime Minister selects Major Gilber Singh
as the Commander of the Rescue Team'
'We have received orders from Delhi
to take over this Operation'
Tell me the action plan
If we perform a sudden surprise attack
we can rescue everyone
It's a go
Strike the enemy
[tense music intensifies]
Military, para military,
Marine Commandos, NSG
Reserve police, Commando, Garud
Every unit has landed, bhai
How will we manage?
'Governor, Chief Minister and
all others to be rescued shortly'
'As announced by
the Army Commander'
Drive to DGP office
[struggling and grunting]
Start the car
'Anna, DC has been nabbed'
'I will be there in 10 minutes'
'Get me past the police barricade
and take me into the DGP office'
Hey!
Thalapathy
Not just you
No one can enter that office
Stored in there
'RC Warfare weapons'
Soldiers
Only 25 terrorists are inside
'If we surround the building'
'And attack all sides
at the same time'
'Easily we can secure it'
- 'How is the josh?
- High, sir'
POSITION
AND MARCH
[uplifting, tense music]
RC War
Begins here
[huge explosion]
HALT
[ongoing explosions]
[menacing music]
Terrorists are coming
ATTACK!
[helicopter rotors whir]
[metallic stomping]
[rapid gunfire]
Shoot that robot!
[helicopter rotors whir]
[screams]
[massive explosion]
[sinister, upbeat music]
[rapid gunfire]
[relentless explosions]
[loud thud]
Clear the premises
We are taking over from here
[gunfire echoes]
[successive explosions]
[tense music intensifies]
[sounds of a struggle]
[grunts and strains]
[glass shatters]
[explosions continue]
May Day!
May Day! May Day!!
[helicopter engine whirs, then explodes]
[screams and cries]
[gunshot]
[laughter]
'Even if you bring in
the entire Indian Military here'
You can't touch me
Not even one strand of hair!
'Shut your gob and obey me'
'Govt bows down to the threats
and demands of the terrorists'
Lock the station door
'Shut down of police stations
throughout Tamil Nadu'
[door locks]
Salman
Escalate to the next level
[grunts]
Governor
Announce that Pakistan terrorists
are gunning down only Hindus
Is that so?
[rapid gunfire]
'Pakistan terrorists are
gunning down only Hindus'
'Somehow save them please'
'Killing all the Hindus'
'We will make India
a Muslim country'
[hesitant music]
'All over Tamil Nadu
in various districts'
'Shops and houses under attack'
Hey! Come out
[sinister vocals]
'Save us, uncle'
[indistinct shouting]
[muffled cries]
Hey! How can we enter the DGP office?
Tell me, da
Only scientist Khaleel is equipped
With weapons to counter the attack
We have kidnapped him too
Hey! Where have you kept
scientist Khaleel captive?
TELL ME
BLURT IT OUT, MAN
[flesh squelches]
Ur-ban
'Square Building'
Who are you, sir?
You can't come in here
[rapid gunfire]
Khaleel
Look at me
Do you remember this girl?
[tense music intensifies]
I am her dad
'Ex-police'
Himmler has attacked
the DGP office
He is holding the Chief Minister,
Governor and others captive
Only if we barge into DGP office
and kill Himmler
We can prevent the weapons
reaching the people's hands
But
They are attacking
with RC War weapons
Weapons I invented to prevent
such a holocaust of a war
Evidence regarding Himmler
My assistants have proof
in my Safe House
Where is that Safe House?
Victor, take the last strike
to the next stage
As per our plan
blast only 1 temple
The attackers are
only Muslims and Christians
Spread this false news in social media
[temple bell chimes]
[eerie music]
[tense music]
[mobile chimes]
Now take the guns to the people
If they clutch the guns in their hands
Our mission is accomplished
We can leave
They have destroyed our temple
We must raze their mosque
and church to the ground
Pick up the guns
[tense music intensifies]
Don't spare a single 'bhai'
'We will rise'
'For justice
We will rise'
They are coming to demolish our mosque
We can't keep quiet any longer
Before that, let us
demolish their temple
'You touch us, face our fury
Push our luck, taste injury'
If anyone dares to target our church
Gun him down
- Hereafter
- Our rule
- From now on
'Spread of weapons
throughout Tamil Nadu'
'Danger of eruption of a civil war'
'Tamil Nadu struggles without
a leader to protect her people'
[soaring orchestral music]
Khaleel is safe
Don't worry
- Thank you so much, anna
- Where are the weapons?
'This is the high frequency interceptor
armored truck built by Khaleel sir'
'This truck will bear the onslaught
of any kind of attack for 10 minutes'
'But after that, if attack continues
the truck will collapse'
'Bullet proof dress for the driver'
We have 3 laser guns, sir
'It will destroy electronic parts'
'These are interceptor guns'
'For cutting remote frequencies'
Can we handle all their weapons
with just these prototypes?
No, ma'am
As per our research
They can be used in 2 ways
One is operated manually
The other is programmed and operated
We have to plan differently
to tackle both options
What plan?
Friendly fire
Machine does not have thinking capacity
The machine will attack
whoever is programmed as enemy
It will even attack its own troop!
How?
Religious fanaticism
and caste-fueled fury
If we program such rage
They incite riots amongst themselves
and bomb blast each other
- Like that?
- Yes, sir
But friendly fire
If we have to program
their machine
We need access to the control room
in that specific building
I got a plan
Prepare yourself
Kayal
Record what I am about to speak now
'My helicopter will land now
No one should obstruct it'
One of you has to accompany me
as a safety measure for me
'30th minute after this'
Everyone will be freed
Who is going in his helicopter?
We are ready, sir
Evidence is in this drive
You remember our plan?
Take care
Viji will come with me
Why take this risk?
Let her come with me
Not only because of people's fear
We need to arrive at a decision
for Viji's fear phobia too
[tense music intensifies]
[drone whirs]
'Bhai, an unknown drone
is crossing our area'
Follow that drone
'That drone has entered
an armored truck'
'Get close to it'
[tense music intensifies]
Blast him
[rapid gunfire]
[explosion]
[tense music intensifies]
Heavy signal jammers for 10 meters
- Can't edge closer
- Shoot from the distance
[rapid gunfire]
'Armor down, 83%'
[tense music intensifies]
'57%'
[upbeat music]
[bullets strike metal]
'Missile activated'
[upbeat music]
[gunfire]
[explosion]
DAMN!
Launch the 'Big boys'
CHITHAA!
[screams]
[tires screech as the car swerves]
[rapid gunfire]
'10 - 9 - 8'
'7 - 6 - 5 - 4'
'Activate'
[heavy gunshots]
[tense music intensifies]
Teju, lock the door
'25%'
[rapid gunfire]
'20%'
[metal door clangs open]
'9%'
[rapid gunfire]
[fists thud and grunts]
'6%'
'4%'
'1%'
[machine emits a chime]
[loud banging]
YES!
YES!!
[tense music intensifies]
[machine rumbles]
[rapid gunfire]
He should not be allowed to enter
You're okay?
'Close a pending case
and I'm on the next major sequel'
'Castin' brighter lights,
wardin' off all the evil'
'See you slippin' I may
go the lengths to seize you'
Tell them to stop
giving guns to the public
[devilish laughter]
In a short while
Hindus will demolish
churches and mosques
Muslims and Christians
will knock down temples
After that, India will face permanent
chaos and communal violence
In a couple of years, arms will multiply
and democracy will crumble and collapse
Then I'll blow the conch and
send democracy to its cemetery
And I will be king of this country
Son, don't be hasty
If this bomb explodes
not only us
Innocent public will die too
Aspiring for power and position
how many more dramas will you enact, sir?
Drama... me?
What are you saying, son?
My daughter gave you a file
in a college function
How did it land in his hands?
I gave that file to
Chief Secretary Leela Rani
'She read through it and told me'
'Nothing to worry, sir
I will handle this'
'Leela Rani is my girlfriend'
'We were batch mates in UPSC training'
'Our dream was to make India
sit up and take notice of us'
'What's your plan?'
- M-M
- M-M?
Important officers never attend
the same function together
I will handle this
[villainous laughter]
CHITHA!
Watch democracy collapse
and then die, da
'Raze the mosque to the ground
Not a trace should remain'
[tumultuous shouting]
'HEY! Shoot whoever comes in between'
'Raze the temple to the ground, da'
'Destroy the church'
'If anyone intervenes shoot at sight'
'In 1 hour, there should be
no trace of that church'
'Reduce the mosque to rubble'
'Demolish the church'
'Knock down the temple'
Even if a single stone
gets damaged in the dome
Not one of you will
get out of here alive
If you lay your hand on our church
You will be headless!
We'll make mincemeat out of you
Chase them away
'Hindus who prevented
the demolition of mosques'
'Muslims who prevented
the destruction of temples'
'Throughout Tamil Nadu'
'People belonging to one religion are
guarding the place of worship of another'
'This is negating the fear of
full-scale revolt among the people'
'Police department continues to seize
the firearms and neutralizing them'
[triumphant laughter]
[overjoyed laughter]
[whistling]
[jubilant laughter]
[mock-cough]
Excuse me
[one last laugh]
'Himmler alias Amrish Pujari
Ex-Deputy Commissioner'
'Evidence confirms him being
the key perpetrator of this major revolt'
[anguished cry of disbelief]
NO...!
HOW IS THIS POSSIBLE?
HOW DID YOU DO THIS, DA?
[rejoicing 'victory']
That is Tamil Nadu for you, da!
Evidence is in this drive
'You remember our plan?'
'Hi, sir'
The angel who gave me rebirth!
My treasure
Thalapathy!
Just tell me what I should do
I will follow your orders
'I have sent some evidence
and videos with my speech'
Dispatch the video to
all police stations in Tamil Nadu
'Why is my Thalapathy not spreading
this evidence on social media?'
'But sending it instead
to police stations?'
Sir, if we spread it, social media
will be able to prevent it today
'But the seed of hatred he has sown
in people's hearts should rot'
'Humanity and tolerance
should grow instead'
Religious extremism should be
prevented in our history forever
Thalapathy has said so
How?
'You would've watched
the evidence I sent'
'You know, Muslim terrorists have not
seized DGP office as a bargaining tool'
'If you are still sitting
inside the station without reacting'
'India is the next Africa!'
'Riot, rebellion, bomb blasts, guns'
'Behind these are
not religion or people'
'Make the public understand it is sheer
power madness and materialistic greed'
Prevent violence
Violence comes from hatred
Hatred comes from threat
Threat comes from
Dirty politics...!
All of us have to join hands
and clear that dirty politics
[loud whistle]
'All beings are equal in birth
But work decides their varied worth'
We are well aware
[laughter of 'victory']
NO
[panic attack]
You lost
Not only democracy
No one on earth can destroy
our beloved democratic leader, da
[appreciative whistle]
He is hitting you and
you are happily taking it
Fear flew far away!
Kill them
Son of King Ravana
Stand-alone Yama in the arena
Every reflection is his own
Leader of the universe; well-known
Come and touch me if you dare
Blood will spurt for all I care
Who is the bull(y) that dares to fight?
Our leader is the symbol of light
A deadly tilt in his stride
Power coiling in every nerve inside
Your blessed fate to be hit
Into a spin swift
your brain will split
Do you have the warrior-spirit?
Or hollow pride of unscaled summit?
Madness to provoke him, you moron
Is your face not yet swollen?
A hero of flame; victory-star
Whoever defies, limbs will char
Once his true colors come to light
You'll freeze; blessed or cursed plight
You could script his life as dialogue
He serves his foes an epilogue
His tale transcends every monologue
Send an enemy, he will simply smile
As if he is used to it; that's his style
Son of Ravana, born to command
Like Yama, he needs no second hand
He is the soul in every frame
The universe bows to his name
- Himmler
- Land the chopper on the terrace
- Down... down
- Come on
He has ruined everything
I HAVE LOST!
You've come so far
We can fight another day
Hurry up
Blast!
Do you know why India is hailed
as the biggest democratic country, da?
No other country can boast of
varied castes, religions or languages
Despite such differences
If a nation can co-exist
as 'unity in diversity'
That is only my motherland India
Trying to destroy that democracy
No damn top dog can succeed
No bloody so-called big shot can do so
No goddamn kingpin can succeed
In the name of democracy
A roll-call of names
Countless decisions
'Chaos unrestrained'
We need Dictatorship
One command
This incident will prove
to the whole world
No damn offender can
push India into danger
'That girl's fear phobia'
'And people's fear was erased
by this democracy called'
'Thalapathy'
He got into the arena
with grit and guts
And stood his ground
to save democracy
Will you do the same?
[mobile ringing]
Papampatti villagers
are coming to vote, anna
Sir
- Aiyaiyo!
- 'Where are you off to?'
Come here
How will tomorrow's verdict be, anna?
Sir, will there be a change?
If we want change
First we must be the change!
This battle I fight for every one of you
My heartbeat, blood, pulse & breath anew
As your leader I will stride by your side
Always in my heart all of you will reside
Only one name spells history
subtitled by rekhs
calibrated by pradeep